

Haniyeh Nematollahi

Junior Front-end developer

PROFILE

I'm a quick learner and always open to learning new things eagerly. I love teamwork, I'm not uncritical type of person so I'm crises are welcome to me also I'm such a problem solver and ready for new Challenges. Over past years, I worked in the field of sales and business, but I realized that my interest is not in this so I started studying programming and participating in training courses, and I'm trying to developing myself in this field.

EDUCATION

Master of business

management, E-commerce/Electronic Commerce Islamic Azad University, Science and Research branch

Tehran, Iran

Bachelor Degree Of Urbanism Engineering Art University

Tehran, Iran

COURSES

Front-End Developer kelaasor

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023 | Tehran, Iran HTML,CSS,Java script,React,Git

HTML,CSS Maktabkhooneh.org

May 2023 – Jun 2023 | Tehran, Iran

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Takhfifan

Technical trainee

May 2023 – present | Tehran, Iran JavaScript Integration with third party

Takhfifan

Business line sales supervisor

2021 – present | Tehran, Iran

- Made contract with more than 200 top websites
- coach the team and achieve monthly targets
- Increase revenue and market share over than 120%

Takhfifan

business line sales expert

2018 – 2021 | Tehran, Iran

- Made contract with all websites
- Search and find best offers
- Get discount cod from websites for the customers

SKILLS

HTML,CSS (hard skill) | **Git** (general skill)

JavaScript (hard skill) | **Figma** (general skill)

React (hard skill) | **postman** (general skill)

self management (soft skill)

Teamwork (soft skill)

Problem solving (soft skill)

Adaptability (soft skill)

LANGUAGES

English

